Andrew's Multichannel Audio Importer v0.9.1
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
This program allows you to import 2-channel audio in Grand Theft Auto IV. With it, you can finally replace the original radio, startup and loading audios.
Also you can edit radio music length in sounds.dat15.

Usage:
1) Click on 'IV audio-file', then select the audio file you want to replace;
2) Click on 'MP3/WAV File', then select audio-file with .mp3/.wav extension;
3) In the 'Channel order' select channel sequence. You can check this with OpenIV;
4) If you want to save the original audio, tick the 'Save original IV Audio' box;
5) Click on 'Import'.

Usage Radio Music Length Editor:
1) Load .dat15-file by clocking the corresponding button;
2) Select the needed track from list;
3) Edit its length by typing necessary time in 'Length' with format HH:MM:SS;
4) Click on 'Apply'.

Developer: Andræs
IMA ADPCM Encoder: Flitskikker
Special thanks: Chipsman, L.a.V.07
Program uses SoX by Chris Bagwell